Generation Iron is a documentary film directed by Vlad Yudin.
Generation Iron - examines the professional sport of bodybuilding today and gives the audience front row access to the lives of
the top 7 bodybuilders in the sport as they train to compete in the world's most premiere bodybuilding stage - Mr.
Narrator (voice), played by Mickey Rourke.
Self, played by Michael Jai White.
Self, played by Lou Ferrigno.
Judge, played by Mike Katz.
Self, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Self, played by Phil Heath.
Generation Iron is a 2013 American documentary film which follows the world's leading
professional bodybuilders as they train and compete for the 2012 Mr.
Considered to be a spiritual sequel to the 1977 documentary Pumping Iron, the film gives access to the lives of the
top seven bodybuilders in the sport, including Phil Heath, Kai Greene, Branch Warren, and Dennis Wolf.
The film is narrated by Mickey Rourke, and features appearances by
Arnold Schwarzenegger, Lou Ferrigno, and Jay Cutler.
The film is directed by Vlad Yudin and produced by Edwin Mejia Jr.
at The Vladar Company and Generation Iron Brands.
The film explores themes of competition, bodybuilding, sport competition.